Cinderella's Sister
Episode 8
Joon Soo.
Was he moved to a larger hospital in Seoul? Is the surgery over?
Not yet?
Hyo Seon and I will get on the first flight tomorrow.
Everything we did here went well.
Are you listening?
Hyo Seon did it. If it wasn't for her, it wouldn't have worked.
Just focus and wait.
It's possible for things like that to happen at his age. Because we responded quickly, nothing bad will happen.
Hello? Hello?
Eun Jo? Eun Jo!
Eun Jo... Are you listening?
Is it because... of me?
There's no chance. I didn't come all the way here to collapse now.
Try it. Jesus, Buddha, the dieties.
If you're going to do something, try it.
If you've jam-packed my life on accident with all the misfortune
you should've spread out to others,
you should know what kind of wretch I am.
I can't stop here. I won't.
Hyo Seon, just like what they said
because my mom and I
only bring misfortune...
are we eating up
ordinary people?
There's no need to worry. The surgery went well, and the critical period has passed.
Of course.
Excuse me?
Did you think something bad would happen?
Dad collapsed with acute myocardial infarction caused by psychogenic shock,
he almost died after getting emergency surgery.
I'm not there, but here.
Please think a bit about who should be the most consoled right now.
You should try to get some rest. Sleep here. I'll come wake you up.
Dad?
Dad...
Why did you do that? Why?
Why did you do that?
Don't cry. He's already having a difficult time.
Let's head in now.
I'm okay. The weather is nice, and so is the breeze.
They said you shouldn't push yourself.
I'm telling you I'm fine.
You can't. You should listen, Dear.
I'm really okay.
They said not to! Why won't you listen?
You can't.
Okay. I'll listen then.
How many times do I have to tell you? I said no salt.
The doctors said he can't have salty foods, why won't you listen?
It's not salty...
What? Not salty? I'm telling you it's salty, but not salty?
Are you saying that I'm calling something not salty, salty? Are you telling me I'm a crazy person?
That's not what I meant ...
We'll redo it. We were wrong, okay? We did wrong.
We'll completely remake it,
so please don't be angry, Joon Soo's mom.
Joon Soo's Mom? Are you my senior?
I'm sorry, ma'am. I did wrong. We'll hurry up and remake it.
Bring me the boiled seaweed. I'm going to remake it.
Um, excuse me... We're all out of the boiled seaweed...
Hyo Seon! What brings you here, without even calling?
Can you give me one set of the best hiking clothes?
Hey. It's been so long, but you won't even greet me?
If you head right into the point like that, I'm grateful.
Who's going to wear it? Are you going to hike?
No. It's for my dad.
Your dad?
When he gets better, he needs to exercise a bit.
I see... But...
Well, sure! Having two sets won't hurt. Follow me.
Two sets? What do you mean?
A little while ago, your sister bought a set of clothes.
Eun Jo, your sister.
While you were in the hospital, we signed contracts with 7 top luxury hotels in Tokyo.
And we have completed the third delivery today.
It'll go well. It will become a sign of the future.
I'm happy that you're here.
Does your father know that you're here?
He doesn't, does he? Let me meet your father.
What?
When you were young, taking you in was an adult taking care of a child.
It was something that I could do and it was doable.
But right now, I seem like I have no conscience.
Ahjussi.
For sure, your father also has other plans for you.
That's why I can't hold you back
Ahjussi, it's not like that.
What do you know, punk? Have you given birth to a child?
Your father had said that he would not utter it.
You can't suspect your father's heart.
My father is different from you.
Of course he is different.
Because he is different, he can protect that big company along with his many employees and family.
That's not it.
I should meet him to see if he is or isn't.
Don't meet him. I will go and meet him.
It will soon happen someday. Please let me do it.
Okay. Not someday, but make sure it will happen.
Ahjussi.
Say it.
You have to trust me.
Whatever happens, even if something unexpected happens.
Please trust me.
"Trust me" is such a nice phrase to hear. Even that kid Hyo Seong asks me to trust her.
And next is you? It's so dependable so it's all good.
Where are you going?
Meet the Japanese buyer alone or take Hyo Seong with you. I can't go.
What are you saying? I purposely brought Gi Hoon to go with you.
Please be careful.
Here.
I will be getting some.
You came to get this? What are you going to do with it?
I wanted to do some heat treatments with it.
- Heat treatments?
- Yes.
If we use heat to kill the harmful strains, we should be able to make a consistent liquor.
If we were to succeed even if we don't ferment it separately then we can get a better alcohol.
Then, we can reduce the processing time and it's possible we can reduce the cost of production.
Wait, wait. If you apply heat treatments,
Will it only kill just the harmful ones? Wouldn't it also weaken the good yeast strains too?
We just have to adjust the fermentation environment. I need to go now.
Go on in.
Eun Jo
I'm wearing this.
Yes.
Isn't it pretty?
It is pretty, Dad!
You are so cool. Unni bought you that?
I also went to her store.
But Unni already bought it first.
You picked a good color.
She called multiple times.
She said to come since the store opened.
I couldn't dare not stop by since I went to Seoul on purpose.
Unni, you bought the gift for Dad but why are you giving excuses to me?
As if you were afraid I would get mad if you said you did that because you were thinking of Dad?
Unni, I'm not 16 anymore.
Dad. It's unfair because of Unni.
That's right, it feels unfair to me too. So you just bought something from your friend's store
and just tossed it to me?
I will be going now.
Are you going to the lab?
Dad, let's take her there.
He just came from there. He needs to rest now.
Dad, it's okay, right? I will be the one driving.
You need to go with Gi Hoon.
Shall I go and see how good you are with dealing with the buyers?
♫  Even if there are wounds left in my heart now ♫
♫  I am told to forget about you ♫
♫  but even if I bite my lips and bear it ♫
♫ My love, you are the only one.♫
The secret to the taste of the makgeoli ( rice wine)
is in a special yeast.
The yeast was created by my father.
You're so cute. I would like to have a drink alone with you.
Thank you for the compliment.
♫ So I can't laugh ♫
♫  I call out your name again ♫
What? Say that again, Oppa.
What did I do?
Who taught you to act like that?
That's why I'm asking what I did?
Don't you know what it means "to have a drink separately?"
For what reason did you agree for such a proposal? Are you that kind of girl?
What?
I told you we are doing business and not selling alcohol.
Are you done talking?
You didn't do business today. Know how to be ashamed.
Then why did you accept the invitation then?
Why did you agree for us to go to her house, eat her food, drink with her,
sign an autograph for that child and take a picture with him as well?!
I did that for a pitiful someone without a mother.
I didn't sell my smile.
What did you say?
Then... are you saying I sold mine?
To those Japanese? Did I?
Oppa! How could you...
How could you say that to me?
Is that something you should be saying to me?
Is that something you really should be saying to me?
It's okay.
Are you okay?
- My heart...
- What?
Your heart?
Does it hurt?
Are you having a hard time breathing?
I'm asking if you are hurt?
My heart is fluttering, Oppa.
♫  Leaving behind the time ♫
My heart is just... beating fast.
♫  I said I longed for you ♫
I'm shaking.
It's not cold but I'm shaking.
♫  doesn't know that I longed for you ♫
♫  Looking only in this direction my two eyes ♫
Move over to the driver's seat. I'm going to push from outside.
♫  If I can always look at you ♫
♫  The day I return to your side again come again ♫
I was wondering if you are eating since you haven't gone home in days.
Ahjumma was curious if you were eating.
Mom?
Is it delicious?
Delicious, right?
You can cook some.
It's not me. It's ahjumma.
My mom doesn't do these things. She hasn't done so for my whole life.
Why are you lying so uselessly?
My mom probably thinks I'm sleeping at home now.
As if. Why would she?
My mom, she doesn't know who you are, right?
That is... who would have imagined I grew up to be this handsome.
You... how did you say you knew I was in this house?
Dae Seong True Wine Makers Liquor, expanding quickly into the market.
- So?
- What?
So? After you saw me in a magazine, what did you do?
Ah, after that?
I searched for the number and called asking to wait since I will seek employment after I get discharged.
I kept calling twice a day.
Oh yeah, Hyungnim came home.
Hyungnim, I just... committed a huge sin.
I must have lost my mind for a while.
I couldn't just be forever living in your shadows just leeching off of you...
and I just... wanted to use my strength to go on my own
so I could stand shoulder-to-shoulder with you and compete fairly.
You wanted to be independent from me.
So you stole from me and made a fake?
That's why my head is not in the right place, Hyungnim.
My brain wasn't good ever since birth.
So that's why my father is to blame for all this. It's my father's fault.
Because Father kept on being terrible to Mom.
My mom wanted to get rid of me who is in her belly so she must have drank some soy sauce or vinegar.
Stand up.
It's not even just vinegar and soy cause but from what I've heard probably some pepper powder too...
Stand up. Now!
Yes, Hyungnim.
Until when are you going to live like this? How old are you already?
You are past the age of marriage and still living off your brother-in-law and causing trouble.
I know, right.
Do you think I wasn't thinking of you?
You are Hyo Seong's only uncle.
I was thinking of having you be independent and married off as part of my responsibility.
You didn't know that and caused this trouble?
- Hae Jin.
- Yes, Hyungnim.
Without me, what will you do?
Pardon?
No one knows what will happen.
Without me, do you think it will be easy for you to stay in this house?
Are you going somewhere, Hyungnim?
Where are you going?
Let go! Let go! Where are you taking me?
Follow me! If you caused trouble then you should take responsibility.
Let go!
Jeong Woo! Tie him up. Tie him and bring him to the police station.
What are you doing, Noona?
No, Hyungnim isn't doing anything about it,
so why are you making a fuss?
Go and come with me to confess to the police.
We've been branded completely as merchants who sell fake liquor right now.
The factory has stopped!
There are no orders coming in from anywhere in the country.
Hurry and go!
Let go! Won't you let this go! I said let go!
Take responsibility! Then we will be able to recover!
Grab her.
Hey! What are you doing?!
Go with me! You should surrender.
Go to the police station! If not I will report you!
Who are you to tell my Uncle to turn himself in?
My father has forgiven him!
Turn yoursself in! Turn yourself in!
Let's go to the police station. Turn yourself in!
What is this girl?
You'd better let go of her.
What are you all doing?
Let go! Let go!
Okay. Okay. You need to breathe.
Let me run for you. Where do you need to run to?
Till there?
You already forgot what upset you, right?
Right. I did.
Why?
And your tears all went back, right?
Yeah.
Now, I can do a show, right?
One, two three...
Watch.
♫ Again today my memory led me astray♫
♫ I who am strolling at the end of the street ♫
♫  where you can't hold me again ♫
♫  I ask again about the way. ♫
♫ Saying I want to see you and hold you again ♫
♫ While looking at heaven I'm praying ♫
♫ It must be you. I cannot be without you. ♫
♫  Like this for another day, month or year ♫
♫  I don't mind even if I am hurt. I don't mind even if my heart breaks ♫
♫  Yes, if it's just you, it is enough ♫
♫  because, yes, you are the only one I love. ♫
Look carefully. This moment
might be the moment that changes Daeseong's history.
Isn't that right, Eun Jo?
Makgeolli (Rice wine)
Test 1
Let's proceed with Daeseong.
Yes, I understand.
But are you sure that it won't be risky? It could cause a problem...
Are you crazy? Do you have a death wish?
If the person who is calling me so late is not crazy, then what are you?
You are the one who will wreck everything for me.
Do you think I will be ruined alone?
Even if I were to be ruined, I will kill you before I get ruined.
What are you, brat!
What's that?
What do you mean? It's nothing.
Give me your phone.
What? Are you crazy?
Who is that?
You don't need to know.
Is it Mr. Jang?
Are you crazy? Why are you mentioning him all of a sudden?
Then, is it a different man and not Mr. Jang?
I'm hearing all sorts of things. You don't need to know.
Mom. I could die.
What!
Let's say the containers that I have to be able to tolerate you
are about a hundred small ones.
And that one by one they are broken
now there's only one left.
What are you saying?
And if that one breaks,
I really... will not live.
You btch! Btch! There really is nothing you can't say to your mother!
What! You will not live? If you won't!
No matter how towards Hyo Seon's dad
you don't have any affection for him...
You can't do that, Mom.
That shouldn't be.
To Hyo Seon's dad
if you do something that shouldn't be done, I...
I will go to hell instead of you.
Hell... rather than what you are to me,
would be easier to bear.
I mean it.
- Fine weather, isn't it?
- Fine weather, isn't it? (In Japanese)
Isn't this type of weather pretty good?
Aren't you going to look at the book?
I am.
If you are going to be like this then, I can't do anything with you.
Oppa.
I told you stop being immature.
I am not.
If not then what is it?
I'm not a child.
- What?
- Don't look at me like a child. It hurts my pride.
Just because you saw me since I was a child, do you still see me as a child?
Am I still a schoolgirl that loses stuff all over the place?
I am speeding it up to be mature like an adult.
I am trying hard to be like you!
The one who is trying hard is not studying when she's supposed to be studying.
I like you to death.
What did you say?
What can I do when I like you so much?
Even if you get mad at me or scold me.
Even if you dislike me, look down on me or laugh at me.
Even though you insult me by saying that I am selling my smile.
No matter what you do, I still like you.
What should I do?
If you're such an adult, tell me what to do at this time?
Answer me now.
You don't know, right? You probably don't.
Because this isn't Japanese language,
It's neither math nor management or something you can study.
And also, because I am not Eun Jo.
Right?
Don't taint my name Goo Hyo Seon.
I have nothing to do with you two.
I am not like you who would have my heart hurt over a man.
Do you know that?
You know what kind of person I am.
The moment I see what is in front of me
that person has nothing to do with me.
I... with people I have lived with before
I am used to parting ways with them even with no warning.
Those people whom I have lived with before become people whom I have nothing to do with in an instant.
That... is the easiest thing in the world.
Whether I eat with those people or be rained on.
No matter how well they treat me, for me...
throwing those people out is not hard at all.
It's the same if someone throws me away.
Even if they leave without a word.
It's something that I am good at.
I live while thinking, "they must be good at it too."
Liking to death, that thing...
I don't know about that as much as a cat or a dog would.
So Goo Hyo Seon,
don't drag me in. Just like to death on your own.
Stop right there.
Stop right there!
Let go.
Do you want to get scolded?
If you want to get scolded then follow her.
Eun Jo Test 1#
Please ferment well.
I beg you.
Me too.
I also, even for a second, parting ways with what stole my heart
is nothing to me.
So bad, being emotional for a moment.
When I think of events of the past or the feelings I have in the past
I do bring it up once in a while but that's it.
For me also, just like you ...
it's simple.
I am like that, but you are not.
You... lied.
Don't.
Don't hate me.
You hating me to death,
forcing to forget or to hate me, don't do that. Just don't do anything.
Just...
think I'm not here.
I...
owe so much to this family.
If there is someone who would wreck this family,
I will kill them all.
If you do something bad to Hyo Seon
know that you will die in my hands.
Open it.
Should I open it?
No. I will.
Scum has formed.
The yeast is still alive. It's not completely ruined yet.
- You should spread some flour...
- No. I will throw it away.
Go and tell them to spread flour and set it aside. It will be fine to drink with the family.
I said I will throw it away!
It's something that Dad was not able to do.
Did you think you would be able to do it?
Dad... because he let you be
did you think he believed that you would succeed?
Can you be quiet? It's noisy.
You... want to be a heroine, right?
If you go ta-da and discover a yeast strain that's publishable
then the factory that my uncle ruined
you'd be able to say that you'd saved it.
You wanted to boast, right?
What to do?
The heroine is not you.
The buyer that I met has placed an order today.
Big enough to the extent that we're not able to fill that order because we don't have enough equipment, and
because we don't have enough money to make alcohol, it's to the point where we can't even take that order.
Is that true?
Why? Because I achieved it, are you riled up?
Please give me money. I need a lot.
I will repay it so lend it.
So, I decided not to take the order.
President, if it's about the money--
No need.
There's no need to consider. The decision has been made.
President.
Don't overdo it. We are not in the situation to be able to handle that order.
I accepted the order.
You accepted the order?
Yes..
What are you planning to do?
I don't have the money to move the lines.
I have maxed out on the loan and there's no way.
I settled it.
We just need to gather a little money.
I went around and begged the family elders.
Elder Dang Sook gave her land deed.
Great grandfather loaned us the money he'd saved to send his grandson to study abroad.
What?
You...
How could you do that without telling me?
The elders, not because of me
but because of Daeseong
when I told the family that it's a way for it to stand up again
they did not hesitate a lot and gave their permission.
Let's do it.
I hope we would do it. We can just do well.
I can find a way for the amount of money we lack.
- Put in four on each side please.
- Yes.
Ahjussi! Please wrap it nicely.
You are working all day at the factory.
What are you doing even late at night?
Do you want to collapse like me?
It's moju. Drink it.
Are you working on yeast again?
Would the fermenting way be the wrong procedure?
What was the problem?
I also don't know.
I really don't know.
Whether it was the wind, the water, the sun,
or if it's the night dew that does it, I really don't know.
But, the yeast you're looking for is everywhere.
Your mom and you
after you both came, the taste of the alcohol has been better.
So the cooperative will definitely rise again.
That's how it was.
The alcohol became deeper.
That...
That's because of the yeast that followed you.
You and your mom
brought it good taste and came to me.
Are you sincere?
Do you think I would be lying?
To look good to you?
Weren't we badly fated mother and daughter?
You...
You... will you call me father even once?
You won't?
If you keep asking me
I... might need to stand and leave.
Okay.
I know how you feel.
King Pigfeet and Bossam.
Welcome.
What is it?
You said you would send money but did not.
You said you would call but did not. You said you would meet me but would not.
I can't take it anymore...
- Coffee please.
- Alright.
I... will not meet you anymore.
You already said that more than a hundred times.
It's true.
You also said that more than a hundred times.
I... will pledge my loyalty to my husband.
You love me but you are loyal to your husband.
I don't care what you do
but being called the same as you
quit it before I rip your mouth.
Wench! Look at how you talk.
Your mouth sure is clean.
If my man dies then you become nothing.
Are you crazy?
It took me a lot to get it. It took me a lot to make it.
So you want me to just buzz off?
Yeah.
Kang Sook.
When I leave, count that money.
You will be satisfied.
It's money I set aside for Eun Jo. I liquidated a huge chunk of it to bring it here.
So don't use it alcohol
Rent a room and live like a person.
You want me to have the money instead of you?
Why are you doing this to me?
What do you see me as?
After I leave, count that money
and if you still want to trade me for that money
then come and catch me.
I will live with you.
₩10,000,000
You... why...
No. I tell you it's not.
No.
What are you denying?
Let's go. I will tell you on the way.
Let's go. I'll tell you everything, okay?
♫ It must be you ♫
♫  I cannot be without you ♫
♫  Like this for another day, month or year ♫
♫  I don't mind even if I am hurt ♫
♫  I don't mind if my heart breaks ♫
♫  because, yes, you are the only one I love. ♫
♫ My bruised heart ♫
♫ is shouting so that I can find you ♫
♫ Wherever you are ♫